[
    {
        "grade": 7,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "When 2 dice are rolled, what is the most likley sum of their values?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "7"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the second planet from the sun?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Venus",
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "What is an adverb?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "A word or phrase that modifies or qualifies an adjective, verb, or other adverb or a word group, expressing a relation of something.",
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "Who was the king who imprisoned Daniel in the lion's den?",
                "isMultiChoice": true,
                "answers": ["Alexander the Great", "Xerxes", "Darius", "Nebuchadnezzar"],
                "correctIndex": 2,
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "Who plays Elsa in Frozen?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Idina Menzel",
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "Guess the Song",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "The Office Theme Song"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "grade": 8,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "What are the three main types of rock?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Igneous, Sedimentary, Metamorphic"
            },
            {
                "question": "Simplify $\\frac{\\left( 4x^{3}\\right)^{2}}{x^{2}}$",
                "isMultiChoice": true,
                "answers": ["$4x^{3}$", "$\\frac{16x^{6}}{x^{2}}$", "$16x^{3}$", "$16x^{4}$"],
                "correctIndex": 3,
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "Towards the end of Second Hand Lions, who is the man in the helicopter related to?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "The Sheik",
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "Who defeated the Saxons at the Battle of Hastings?",
                "isMultiChoice": true,
                "answers": [
                    "Harold Godwinson",
                    "William the Conqueror",
                    "Edward the Confessor",
                    "Charles the Bald"
                ],
                "correctIndex": 1,
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the only US state that begins with the letter P?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Pennsylvania",
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "Guess the Song",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Celine Dion - My Heart Will Go On"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "grade": 9,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Expand $(2x+3y)^{2}$",
                "isMultiChoice": true,
                "answers": [
                    "$4x^{2}+6xy+3y^{2}$",
                    "$13x^{2} y^{2}$",
                    "$4x^{2} +9y^{2}$",
                    "$4x^{2} +12xy+9y^{2}$"
                ],
                "correctIndex": 3
            },
            {
                "question": "What are diverging boundaries?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Where tectonic plates are moving apart from each other in opposite directions",
                "time": 30
            },

            {
                "question": "Who wrote Chinese Cinderella?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Adeline Yen Mah",
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "When was the Industrial Revolution?",
                "isMultiChoice": true,
                "answers": ["1450 - 1780", "1760 - 1840", "1830 - 1910", "1939 - 1945"],
                "correctIndex": 1,
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "How many British Monarchs were named George? (How many King George's)?",
                "isMultiChoice": true,
                "answers": ["6", "10", "2", "4"],
                "correctIndex": 0,
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "Guess the Song",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Tears for Fears - Everybody Wants To Rule The World"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "grade": 10,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "What are the first five elements of the periodic table?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Hydrogen, Helium, Lithium, Beryllium, Boron"
            },
            {
                "question": "Calculate the distance between the points (-3, 4) and (5, 10)",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "10",
                "time": 60
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of these sentences uses semicolons correctly?",
                "isMultiChoice": true,
                "answers": [
                    "Although they tried; they failed.",
                    "Dante Martinez, a registered nurse; Susan Brooks, a dietician; and Chien-Ling Ko, a physical therapist, attended the meeting.",
                    "The conference has people who have come from Moscow, Idaho; Springfield, California, Alamo, Tennessee, and other places as well.",
                    "According to my calculations; it should definitely work."
                ],
                "correctIndex": 1,
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "Who was the first king of Rome?",
                "isMultiChoice": true,
                "answers": ["Romulus", "Alexander the Great", "Constantine", "Augustus"],
                "correctIndex": 0,
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "What is a group of crows called?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "A murder",
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "Guess the Song",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Run DMC - Walk This Way"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "grade": 11,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "What is the energy carrying molecule of the cell?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Adenosine Triphosphate (ATP)"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the turning point of $y=( 2x-5)^{2} +3$",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "(2.5, 3)",
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "What nationality is Gibson from the Dunkirk movie?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "French",
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "Which famous Jacobin leader led the Reign of Terror during the French Revolution?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Maximilien Robespierre",
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "In what country was the first electric car ever built?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Germany",
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "Guess the Song",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Nirvana - Come As You Are"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "grade": 12,
        "questions": [
            {
                "question": "Given the reaction $aA+bB\\rightleftharpoons cC+dD$, what is the equation for the equilibrium constant?",
                "isMultiChoice": true,
                "answers": [
                    "$K_{c} =\\frac{[ C]^{c}[ D]^{d}}{[ A]^{a}[ B]^{b}}$",
                    "$K_{c} =\\frac{c[ C] d[ D]}{a[ A] b[ B]}$",
                    "$K_{c} =\\frac{cd[ A][ B]}{ab[ C][ D]}$",
                    "$K_{c} =\\frac{[ A]^{a}[ B]^{b}}{[ C]^{c}[ D]^{d}}$"
                ],
                "correctIndex": 0
            },
            {
                "question": "Differentiate the following function: $5e^{2x} +\\ln\\left( x^{2}\\right)$",
                "isMultiChoice": true,
                "answers": [
                    "$10e^{x} +\\frac{x}{x^{2}}$",
                    "$5e^{2x} +\\frac{2x}{x^{2}}$",
                    "$10e^{2x} +\\frac{2}{x}$",
                    "$\\frac{5}{2} e^{2x} +2x\\ln( x)$"
                ],
                "correctIndex": 2,
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "Over what part of Long Island do the eyes of Dr. T.J. Eckleberg watch over?",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "The Valley of Ashes",
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year did Adolf Hitler become Chancellor of Germany?",
                "isMultiChoice": true,
                "answers": ["1939", "1933", "1945", "1935"],
                "correctIndex": 1,
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the radius of pluto? (The 2 closest teams will win)",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "1188km",
                "time": 30
            },
            {
                "question": "Guess the Song",
                "isMultiChoice": false,
                "answer": "Wild Cherry - Play That Funky Music"
            }
        ]
    }
]
